Finding Aid for the Collection of Pamphlet Maps LSC.0990
UCLA Library Special Collections
- [Card files]
  - Carte de la terre ferme, du Perou, du Bresil, et du pays des Amazones, dressée sur les méoires les plus nouveaux & les observations les plus exactes., [1719]; map.; 1. South America - Maps. (Box 35)
    Tom VI, no, 31, pag. 122. [from Chatelain: Atlas historique, 1705-1720.
    Cf. Lowery, p.224.
  - Chamberlin, Daniel W
    See the following entry in this catalog: Progressive map service. Map of. county, California, ca.1916.
  - Chafrión, José 1653-1698.
    See the following entry in this catalog: Dury, Andrew - A topographical map of the republic of Genoua. 1764.
  - Map of the City of Los Angeles. [San Francisco], 1922.; 1 map. 56 x 43cm. (Box 32)
    No scale indicated.
    On verso: Chadwick's automobile road map of Southern California.
    Tipped into pamphlet: The Golden Gate auto road guide covering California. 1920. With sectional road maps of the state and of principal cities.
  - Chadwick's automobile road map of California [San Francisco], 1918.; 1 map. 54 x 43cm. (Box 32)
    [Removed for cataloging 4/93] [JD??]
  - Cruchley's county map of Bedford & improved from the ordnance surveys. London, Gall & Inglis, 1875?; Col. map.; 1. Gt. Brit. - Maps. (Box 8)
    Series: Cruchley's county maps of England.
  - unspecified, Collection of maps. (Card 3); 1. [Each state mentioned] - Maps; (Box 27)
    I. Colton, Charles B, 1832-1916, pub.
  - Colton, George Woolworth, 1827-1901, pub.; Collection of maps. (Card, 2) (Box 27)
    G. Woolworth Colton's new guide map of the United States & Canada, with railroads, counties, etc., 1861 (publ. Chicago, Blanchard); 1875.-Map of part of the United States north of the 37th.parallel, embracing the country between the Atlantic Ocean and the 96th meridian of longitude, cl869.-Colton's road map of the counties of Orange and Rockland, state of New York, 1893.
  - New York, G.W. & C.B. Colton, 1861-1893; Collection of maps.; 10 maps. (Box 31)
    Colton's map of the state of Alabama, 1883; 1889.- Colton's Florida, 1872.- Colton's map of the state of Mississippi, 1873.- Colton's map of the state of South Carolina, 1866.-Colton's map of the state of Tennessee, 1869.-Colton's Virginia, 1867.
  - Colton, Charles B, 1832-1916, pub.
    See the following entry in this catalog: Colton, George Woolworth, 1827-1901. Collection of maps.
  - Collins, Henry George, publisher.
    See the following entry in this catalog: England depicted, in a series of splendidly full-coloured maps. London [ca.l860?]
  - Collection of maps. Denver, Colo., Clason map co., 1907-1914.; 3 maps.; Map of Nevada and Southern California, 1907;; Map of California, 1914. Map of Arizona, 1911;; l. Area above - Maps. (Box 31)
  - Clason's double indexed map of Chicago. Chicago (Box 32)
  - Clarici, Paul Barthelemi
    See: Clarici, Paolo Bartolomeo, 1664-1725.
  - Map of Abyssinia, Egypt and Nubia, with part of the Mediterranean and the Red sea. London, G.F. Cruchley, 1867.; Col.map.; 1. Africa - Maps. (Box 8)
  - Cruchley's new plan of London, shewing all the new and intended improvements to the present time. London, Cruchley mapsaller, [1840]; Col. map.; 1. London - Maps. (Box 8)
    Title on box: Cruchley's new plan of London in miniature, improved to 1840.
  - Covens, Johannes publisher.
    See the following entry in this catalog: Sedes belli, of de stoel des oorlogs in den landen, van Braband. [ca.1750?]
  - The countries around the Mediterranean sea. London, Edward Stanford, 1886.; Col. map.; 1. Mediterranean region - Maps. (Box 14)
    I. Stanford, Edward, publisher.
  - Official map of Contra Costa County, California. By T.A. McMahon. and Wm. Minto. in accordance with an order of the Honorable Board of supervisors, dated February 4th, 1885. [San Francisco] A.J. Leary, [l885?]; map in 2 sections. 141 x 133 cm. fold to 30 x 21 cm. (Box 28)
    For additional information see public catalog card.
  - Map of Los Angeles City. [Los Angeles?], c. 1905.; 1 map. 44 x 40cm. (Box 32)
    On the verso is: Map of Los Angeles and vicinity showing railways and electric lines radiating from Los Angeles to adjacent points.
  - Collection of maps. New York, J.H. Colton, l853-1864; 9 maps.; Indies, &c., 1864.; 1. [Each state mentioned] - Maps (Box 27)
    Colton's Alabama, 1860.- California, 1853; 1859 (both have insets of San Francisco).- Colton's Louisiana, 1863.- J.H. Colton's topographical map of Virginia, Maryland & Eastn. Tennesee. & part of adjoining states, 1861.- Colton's Virginia, 1861.
    Colton's map of the United States, the Canadas &c., 1864.- Map of the United States of America, the British provinces, Mexico, the West Indies and Central America: with part of New Granada and Venezuela, 1856.-(Colton's map of the Americas, Africa, and a portion of the Atlantic and aprt of the Pacific Oceans:inset in:) Colton's rail-road and military map of the United States, Mexico, the West
  - Plano general de la ciudad de México. Mexico, V. Debray y ca. editors, 1880.; Col.map. (Box 24)
  - Carta general de la República mexicana, formada y corregida con presencia de los últimos datos y el auxilio de las autoridades mas competentes. México, Impa. Litoga. De Debray, 1867.; map. 81x116cm. fold. to 17x11cm.; 1. Mexico - Maps. (Box 25)
    "Escala de leguas mexicans de 26 y ½ al grado."
    Shows "Tabla de distancias; Estado comparativo de la problacion Croquis de los caminos de México, à Vera-Cruz; Comparacion de los principales rios [y montañas]; Perfil[s] del camino[s]
    De México à Veracruz [y Acapulo]"
    Inset maps of the ports of Matamoros, Vera Cruz and Tampico.
    In portfolio.
    Mutilated copy.
  - County of Somerset. Surveyed by Day and Masters. 2nd ed. London, W. Faden, 1800.; Col. map; 1. Gt. Brit, - Maps. (Box 22)
    First published in 1782 by W. Day.
    I. Masters
  - New map of the dowinion of Canada. Edinburg, J. Bartholomewm, 1870.; Col. map.; 1. Canada - Maps. (Box 25)
    Insets: Environs of Montreal; Newfoundland.
  - The boundaries of the boroughs, county court districts, railways, and modern improvements London, Edward Stanford, [ca. 1865?]; Col. map.; 1. London - Maps (Box 35)
  - Davies's map of the environs of London. London, Davies, 1856.; Col.map.; 1. London - Maps (Box 35)
  - Danvbivs, fluvius Europae maximus, a fontibvs ad Ostia, cum omnibus fluminibus, ab utroque latere, in ilium defluentibus., col.map.; 1. Europe, Eastern- Maps. 2. Danube River -Maps. (Box 36)
  - Cruchley's county map of Kent, showing all the railways & names of stations. improved from the Ordnance surveys. London, Ga11 & Inglis, [ca. 1870?]; Col.map.; 1. Gt. Brit. - Maps. (Box 8)
    Cover-title: Cruchley's railway and station map of the county of Kent.
  - A new map of Tennessee, with its roads and distances. Philadelphia, Charles Desilver, 1860.; col.map.; 1. Tennessee -Maps. (Box 31)
    Insets of Environs of Nashvill; Environs of knoxville.
  - Description dv pays armoriqve a pres Bretaigne., map.; 1. France -Maps. (Box 35)
  - Denny's pocket map of.county, 1. [Each county below] - Maps. (Box 29)
    San Mateo, 1913.- San Luis Obispo, 1916.-San Joaquin, 1913.- Santa Barbara, 1916.-Santa Clara, 1913.- Sonoma, 19O7.- Stanislaus, 1912.-Sutter, 1913.- Tulare, 1911. Ventura, 1913.-Iuba, 1913- El Dorado, 1916 (in CF. Weber wrapper).
  - Denny's pocket map of. county, California; a collection. San Francisco, Edward Denny & co., 1910-1916; 21 maps. (Box 29)
    Contra Costa, 1915.- Fresno, 1911.-- Kings, 1912.-Merced, 1912.-Monterey, 1913.-tourists' map of Mt. Tamalpais, 1910.-Napa, 1915.-Orange, 19l5.- San Benito, 1913.-
  - De L'Isle, Joseph Nicolas, 1688-1768.
  - De L'Isle, Guillaume
    See: Delisle, Guillaume, 1675-1726.
  - Map of the empire of Germany, including all the states comprehended under that name; with the kingdom of Prussia, &c. London, Robt. Sayer., [ca.1800]; Col. map.; 1. Germany - Maps (Box 3)
  - Colombia prima or South America. London, W. Faden, 1807.; col.map in 2 sheets; 1. South America - Maps. (Box 9)
  - Carte de l'Algérie, Tell, Kabylie et Sahara Algérien. Paris, Longuet, 1856.; Col.map.; 1. Africa - Maps (Box 13)
  - A topographical map of Hartford-Shire. by Andrew Dury and John Andrews. [London?, ca.1762?]; 2 col.map sheets (Box 6)
    I. Andrews, John, 1736-1809.
  - A topographical map of the republic of Genoua, taken from the celebrated map by Chaffrion; with any additions & improvements. [London] A. Dury, 1764.; Col.map. (2 sheets); 1. Italy - Maps (Box 3)
    I. Chafrión, José, 1653-1698.
  - ...map of the present seat of war, between the Russians, Poles, and Turks. 2nd. ed. London, W. Faden, 1787.; Col.map.; 1. Europe, Eastern - Maps (Box 2)
  - Dufrénoy, Ours Pierre Armand Petit, 1792-1857.
  - Dodson, James, -1757.
    See the following entry in this catalog: Halley, Edmond, 1656-1742. A correct chart of the terraqueous globe. London, 1794.
  - A new map of the county of York, divided into its ridings with their subdivisions. London, William Darton, 1820.; Col.map; 1. Gt. Brit. - Maps (Box 17)
    From Ogden collection
  - Disturnell's treaty map; the map that was part of the Guadalupe Hidalgo treaty on southwestern boundaries, 1848. Text by Jack D. Ritenhouse, Santa Fe, Stagecoach Press, [1965]; 20 p. fold. col. map mounted on cover. 24 cm. (Box 25)
    Bibiliography: p. 20.
    1. Disturnell, John, 1801-1877. 2. Guadalupe Hidalgo, Treaty of, 1848. II. Rittehouse, Jack De Vers, 1912-
    E408.D5 911.7 66-4254
    Library of Congress
  - Disturnell, John, 1801-1877, publisher.
    See the following entry in this catalog: A new map of Central America shewing the different lines of Atlantic & Pacific...
  - Carte du gouvernement de Tauride, comprenant la Krimee et les pays voisins. Paris, Dezauche, 1788.; Col.map.; 1. Russia - Maps (Box 1)
  - Europe, exhibiting its principal states, &c. London, W. Faden, 1817.; Col. map. (Box 22)
    I. Faden, William, 1750-1836, publ.
  - Europe, exhibiting its principal states, &c. London, W. Faden, 1791.; Col.map. (Box 22)
  - Etats de la maison de Brunswick-Luneburg, et de leurs frontieres. Paris, Julien, 1758.; Col.map. (Box 5)
    1. Germany - Maps. I. Julien, Roch-Joseph, publ.
  - Ensign, Bridgman & Fanning's railroad map of the United States, showing the depots & stations. New York, 1856.; map.; 1. U.S. - Maps. (Box 28)
  - Ensign, Bridgman & Fanning's rail road map of the United States, showing the depots & stations. New York, Ensign, Bridgman & Fanning, 1859, c1856.; Col.map.; 1. U.S. - Maps. 2. Railroads - U.S. - Maps. (Box 31)
    Covers area generally east of the Mississippi river.
  - England depicted, in a series of splendidly fall-coloured maps. Yorkshire, N. Riding. London, H.G. Collins, [ca. 1860?]; Col.map.; 1. Gt. Brit. - Maps (Box 17)
    I. Collins, Henry George. publisher.
  - Elie de Beaumont, Léonce, 1794-1874.
  - Edwards, publisher.
  - Nouvelle carte d'Europe physique & routiere. Paris, A.Bes & F. Dubreuil, [1866?]; Col.map.; 1. Europe - Maps. (Box 12)
    Engraved views of cities in borders.
  - Mappe-node ou carte generale de la terre, dressée observations de Mrs. de l' Acadenie Royale des Sciences, Paris, chez l'Auteur, 1717.; map.; 1. World maps (Box 35)
    Ex libris Wareen C. Shearman
  - Les isles Failippines et celles des Larrons ou de Marianes, les isles Moluques et de la Sonde., avec la presquislé de l'Inde da la le Gange ou orientale. Paris, chez l'auteur, 1700.; map.; 1. Islands of the Pacific - Maps. 2. Philippine Islands - Maps. 3. Indonesia - Maps. (Box 35)
  - Les isles de I'Amerique connues sous le nom d 'Antilles, ou sont les isles de Cuba, St. Domingue et Jamaique, les Lucayes, les Caribes, et celles du vent. Paris, chez l'auteur, 1705.; 1. Caribbean area - Maps. (Box 35)
  - Les costes aux environs de la riviere de Misisipi. Decouvertes par Mr. de la Salle en 1683. et reconnues par Mr. le Chevallier d' Iberville, en 1698. et 1699. 1705.; map.; 1. Mississippi river - Charts, maps, etc. 2. Caribbean area - Maps. (Box 35)
    Cf. Lowery Collection, 1912, p.219.
  - Le Candda, ou nouvelle France, la Floride, la Virginie, Pensilvanie, Caroline, nouvelles Angleterre et nouvelle Yorck, 1'isle de terre neuve, la Louisiane et le cours de la riviere de Misisipi. Paris, chez l'auteur, 1705.; map.; 1. America - Maps. (Box 35)
  - Faust's pocket map of city and county of San Francisco. Lithographed in colors. 12th ed. San Francisco, H. W. Faust, c1892.; map. 64½x80 cm. fold. to 18x10 cm.; 1. San Francisco - Description - Maps. (Box 31)
    No scale.
  - Faithorne, William 1616-1691, engr.
    See the following entries in this catalog:
    Heermans, Augustus, 1621?-1686.
    Virginia and Maryland. 1941
  - The sea of Marmara or Propontis, with the Straits of Constantinople and of Gallipoli. London, William Faden, 1786.; Map.; 1. Dardanelles - Charts, maps, etc. (Box 3)
    "This map was originally drawn by P.D. Bohn."
    I. Bohn, P D
  - Nouvrelle carte de la Suisse, dans laquelle sont exactement distingues les treize cantons, leur allies, et leurs sujets. London, Wm. Faden, 1778.; Col.map.; 1. Switzerland - Maps. (Box 2)
  - The graded road map of Scotland. Edinburgh, Gall & Inglis, ca.1900.; 2 maps (Box 18)
    Central Perthshire; Glasgow and Ayr
  - Galiano, Dionisio Alealà
    See: Alealà Galiano, Dionisio, 1760-1805.
  - This trigonometrical plan of the town and port of Liverpool. Liverpool, M.A. Gage, 1836.; Col.map.; 1. Gt. Brit. - Maps (Box 13)
  - Uma carta náutica Portuguesa, anónima, de circa 1471. [Lisbon?] nistério das Colónias, 1940.; 62 p. facs. map.; 1. Maps manuscript - facsimiles; 2. Portugal - Maps. (Box 23)
  - The official map of Orange county, California, and adjoining counties, comp. by S.H. Finley and J.L. McBride, [Santa Ana], 1924.; map.; 1. Orange County, California - Maps. (Box 31)
    c.1923 J.L. McBride.
    I. McBride, J L
  - Map of Virginia and Maryland, constructed from the latest authorities. Philadelphia, A. Finley, 1824.; col.map.; 1. Maryland - Maps. 2. Virginia - Maps. (Box 31)
    Drawn by D.H. Vance; Engraved by J.H. Young
    I, Young, James Hamilton II. Vance, D.H.
  - Map of the United States, constructed from the latest authorities. [Philadelphia, A, Finley, 1824?]; col.map; 1. U.S. - Maps. (Box 31)
    I. Young, James Hamilton II. Vance, D H
  - Voyage d'Enée, tire de Virgile. Paris, chez 1'Auteur, 1705.; map.; 1.Mediterranean region - Maps. (Box 35)
  - Le vieux Mexique ou Nouvelle Espagne auec les costes de la Floride Faisant partie de l'Amerique septentrionale. Paris, chez l'auteur, 1705.; map.; 1. Mexico - Maps. 2. Central America - Maps. (Box 35)
    Cf. Lowery Collection, 1912, p.222.
  - A new and correct chart of the Gulf of Finland. London, Willam Faden, 1785.; Col.map.; 1. Finland, Gulf of - Charts, maps, etc. (Box 4)
    I. Faden, William, publ.
  - Girelli, Pietro Paolo
    See: Cingolani, Giovanni Battista
  - Collection of maps. Portland, Ore., J.K. Gill & co., 1874-1884.; 4 maps.; 1. Washington (State) - Maps. 2. Oregon - Maps. (Box 25)
    New sectional township & county map of Oregon & Washington, 1884.- Habersham's sectional and country map of Oregon, 1874.- Washington Territory, 1878, comp. by Robt. A. Habersham.- New sectional township & country map of Washington, 1884.
    I. Habersham, Robert A
  - Gill, John Kaye
  - General map of the countries comprehended between the Black Sea and the Caspian. London, Edwards, 1788.; Col.map.; 1. Russia - Maps. (Box 3)
    I. Edwards, publ.
  - Geikie, Sir Archibald, 1835-1924.
  - Carta postale ed itineraria d'Italia. Compiled and edited by Antonio Federico Botte. Udine, Litografia Berletti, 1884. (Box 32)
    Map mounted on linen, folded into marble board slipcase.
  - Plano general de la ciudad de Mexico. Levantado en el ano de 1793. Aumentado y corregido. Rafael Maria Calvo en el de, 1830. (Box 24)
    Mexico(City)- Maps I. Calvo, Rafael Maria
  - Das Himalaja Gebirg in Bissahir, Gherwal & Kemaun, von Südrande des plateaus von Mittel-Tibet bis zum Tieflande von Hindostan. Mit besonderer Rücksicht auf Carl Ritter's Allgemeine Erdkunde, II.Buch, Th.2, S.493, such S66 o ff. entworfen and bearbeitet von J. L. Grimm, herausgegeben von C. Ritter and F.A. O'Etzel. Berlin, Geographischen Verlags-Comtoir, 1833. (Box 18)
    Map mounted on linen in cloth case.
    With: 2 charts of elevations for the eastern and western heights.
  - Map of the country of Kent, from an actual survey made in the years, 1819 & 1820.; Col.map; 1. Gt. Brit. - Maps. (Box 26)
    London, published for the proprietors, by G. Pringle junr., 1821
  - Plan of Imberhorne estate, 1899.; Col.map. (Box 21)
    Surveyed in 1873-4; rev. in 1895, and 1897. Southampton,1895.
    Mss. additions outline Imberhorne estate.
  - Monmouthshire., ca. 1885-1886.; 9 map sheets in 3 cases. (Box 21[?])
    Several of these maps show revisions made after the official publication dates.
  - Map of Monastic Britain. Chessington, Surrey., 1950.; 2 sheets. (Box 32)
  - unspecified, col.map in several sheets (Box 21)
    [Chesham, Chesham Bois, Amersham] Surveyed in 1876; Revised in 1897. Reprinted at various dates, by section.
  - Collection of maps England, Scotland, and Ireland. v.p., ca.1809-1925.; ca.100 maps.; 1. Gt. Brit. - Maps (Box 20, 21, 22, 33)
    Most of these maps were prepared in Southampton and London.
    x Ordnance Survey Office, Southampton.
  - Auto roads of. Los Angles, C.J. Gray & co., 1907-1908.; 3 vols.; 1. California - Maps. (Box 32)
    San Francisco and Oakland to Monterey and Santa Cruz, c1908.- Valley route and northern California, c1907.- Central California, c1907.
  - Railroad and country map of Virginia, W. Virginia, Maryland and Delaware. New York, A.A. Grant, [ca.1875]; col.map.; 1. Railroads - U.S. - Maps. 2. [Each state] - Maps. (Box 31)
  - Hartley's map of Arizona from official documents. New York, n.d.; Map.; 1. Arizona - Maps. (Box 25)
    "Drawn and engraved by J.C. Smith; N.Y."
  - General-karte von Australien und der südsee. Revidirt and ergänzt von Otto Herkt. Glogau, Carl Flemming, 1889.; Col.map.; 1. Australia - Maps. 2. Islands of the Pacific - Maps. (Box 25)
  - A correct chart of the terraqueous globe., 1. World maps. (Box 38)
    A correct chart of the terraqueous globe, on which are described lines shewing the variation of the magnetic needle in the most frequented seas, originally composed in the year 1700. renewed by William Mountaine and James Dodson, according to observations made about the year 1756, and now published with all the necessary emendations. London, Laurie & Whittle, 1794.
    I. Mountaine, William, II. Dodson, James,
  - Leigh's new road map of England, Wales and Scotland, drawn from the most recent surveys. London, Samuel Leigh, [ca.1825?]; Col.map.; I. Leigh, Samuel 1. Gt. Brit.-Maps (Box 16)
  - Habersham, Robert A.
    See the following entry in this catalog: Gill, J.K. & co., pub. Collection of maps.
  - Plan métro-omnibus de Paris divisé En vingt arrondissements. Paris, Guilmin, [ca.1855?]; 2 col.maps. Street guide.; 1. Paris - Maps. (Box 24)
    Cover-title.
  - Guide-books: a miscellaneous collection., v.p., v.d.; 10 vols. (Box 11)
    1. Voyages and travels-guide-books. xGuide-books.
  - Das Himalaja Gebirg in Bissahir., 1833. (Box 18)
    Another edition of the map included in Ritter, Karl, Entwurf zu einer Karte vom ganzen Gebrigssysteme des Himalaj. Berlin, 1932. Exlibris C.K. Ogden.
  - Landgrafiatvs Hasso-Cassellanvs. Nuremberg, Homännische erben, 1761.; col.map; 1. Germany - Maps. (Box 4)
  - Reise-, post- and zoll-karte von Deutschland, mit angabe der eilwagen-kurse. Stuttgart, Carl Hoffmann, 1834.; Col.map.; 1. Germany - Maps. (Box 12)
  - Herndon's report. Maps. [Washington, R. Armstrong, public printer, 1854]; 3 maps. (Box 31)
    Part I of the Atlas for Herndon, Wm. Lewis. Exploration of the valley of the Amazon. Washington, 1854. Issued as Senate Ex. Doc. No. 36, 2d sess., 32d cong.
  - Herbert, William
    See the following entry in this catalog: Andrews, John - A topographical-map, of the county of Kent. ca.1765.
  - Official map of the state of Sonora Republic of Mexico, compiled from surveys, reconnoissances and other sources. N.P, c1884.; Col.map.; 1. Mexico - Maps. (Box 25)
    Titles and information in English and Spanish. copyright date 1884; map dates altered to 1885.
  - Hendschel's post and reise karte von Deutschland. gezeichnet and gestochen von Jos. Back & C. Sauter. Frankfurt a/M, ca. 1840.; Col.map; 1. Germany - Maps. (Box 15)
  - Virginia and Maryland as it is planted and inhabited this present year 1670 surveyed and exactly drawne by the only labour & endeavour of Augustin Herrman bohemiensis. W: Faithorne sculpt. London, Sold by John Seller, 1673; Providence, R.I., 1941.; map. 79 x 93cm. on 4 sheets. (Box 23)
    tracings on main cards.
  - Heald-Meanery's geographical, commercial and recreational map of California. San Francisco. Heald-Meanery Schmidt Litho. Co., printers., [1927?]; 44 x 64 in. cut into 8 strips, folded to make a book of 64pp. Issued in conjunction with a Surevey Index (not here.); I. Schmidt Litho Co. 1. California (1927)-Maps. (Box 32)
    Cover title: California Survey.
  - Descriptive map shewing the treaty limits round Yokohama, including the province of Sagami & portions of Kai, Idzu, Musasi & Suraga. London, James Wyld, 1867.; Col.map.; 1. Japan-Maps. (Box 17)
  - Innes, James
    See the following entry in this catalog: Taperell, Nicholas The ancient cities of London and Westminster. [1849]
  - Rajpootana and adjacent countries, compiled from various existing materials in the office of the surveyor general of India to 1846. Calcutta, 1858-59.; map in 4 fold. sections. 31½cm.; 1. India - Maps. (Box 11)
    In case. Scale: 8 British miles = 1 inch.
  - Ignaz, Georg
    See: Metzburg, Georg Ignaz von, freiherrn, 1735-1798.
  - Iakubicska
    See: Jacubicska de Csermend, Stephan, 1742-1806.
  - Map of Oklahoma. Compiled from the official records of the general land office and other authentic sources. Kansas City, Mo., [1891?]; Col.map.; Scale: 8½ miles - 1 inch (Box 32)
    Cover title: New map of Oklahoma, showing the Cherokee Strip. And all Indian reservations.
  - Map of the State of Oregon. Portland, Oregon, Title Guarantee and Trust Co., 1904.; 1 item. 78 x 86cm. Col. map. (Box 32)
    Cover title: Sectionized map of the State of Oregon.
    Ex-libris: Robert E. Cowan.
  - [Unidentified facsimile map of South America], 1558?; col. map. (Box 37)
    Manuscrit sur parchemin. Bibliothèque Nationale de Paris, cartes, Inv. 1021. Ex-libris: Warren C. hearman.
  - Thirty five miles around Richmond, Va. Washington, D.C., C. Bohn, 1867.; Col.map.; 1. Virginia - Maps. (Box 31)
  - Nova comitatus Pappenheimensis. Nureberg, Homann, ca.1761.; col.map; 1. Germany - Maps (Box 4)
    xHomännische erben
  - Stanford's library map of Australasia. London, Edward Stanford, 1859.; Col.map in 4 sheets.; 1. Australasia - Maps. (Box 25)
    I. Stanford, Edward, pub.
  - Johnstons' new map of India. with enlarged Plan of Delhi and its environs. Edinburgh, W. & A.K. Johnston, 1857.; Col.map.; 1. India - Maps. (Box 13)
  - Mappa ou carta geographica dos reinos de Portugale Algarve. Londres, Wm. Faden, 1762.; 2 col.map sheets.; 1. Portugal - Maps. (Box 4)
  - The county of Oxford, surveyed anno mdcclxvi &c. vii; and engraved by Thomas Jefferys. [London?], 1768.; Col.map.; 1. Gt. Brit.- Maps (Box 8)
  - The county of Huntingdon. [London, Jefferys], 1768.; Col.map; 1. Gt. Brit. - Maps (Box 8)
  - Jaillot, Charles Hubert Alexis, 1640-1712.
    See the following entry in this catalog:
    Brion de la Tour, Louis, 1765?-1823.
    L'Amerique divisée. Paris, 1783.
  - Map of the City of san Diego and vicinity, California. San Diego, 1906.; 1 map. 74 x 50cm.; Scale 1:50,000 (Box 32)
    With tract index.